Right now open your lips, open the door of your heart.
Thou power of deliverance!
Everyone that is here today, I speak to your heart and soul.
Every demonic activity within and outside you, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Demonic activity, in the name of Jesus - out of my life!
Begin to command them out!
Command them out!
In the name of Jesus Christ !
She is my daughter. Deliver her for me, Man of God!
Who are you?
I am the woman in the water.
Who is this man?
I don't know him. I am nobody to him.
What do you want to say now?
She's my daughter.
He says you are his daughter.
I'm not his daughter.
Who is he?
I don't know.
Stand up and look at his face.
It's because the one inside of her is the one talking.
The life you people live is a hopeless life - life without the power of God.
Look at your daughter. She is saying that she doesn't know you.
Assuming you had been living in line with the power,
she would not face you to say that she doesn't know you
and you gave birth to her.
Where did you meet the mother?
I met her in Maiduguri, Borno State.
The whole thing started from the connection where you people met.
It was't an issue of marriage but later resulted to it.
At the beginning, it was a different thing.
Yes, sir.
Who are you?
I'm the woman in the water.
How come about the woman in the water? Who is your father then?
I don't have a father.
Who is your mother?
I don't have a mother.
How old are you?
I don't have an age.
Touch your daughter.
I don't know this man.
Carry your daughter.
Your father has carried you.
I said he is not my father.
- But somebody is carrying you.
- Yes.
- Who is he?
- I don't know him.
Somebody you don't know, you allowed the person to carry you.
Why can't you disappear?
I am in somebody's body.
Clap for Jesus Christ!
Did you listen to that?
For you to know that she is not a small girl.
She is telling me things of the spirit. She said, ''I'm in somebody's body''.
He is not carrying the real body that is talking.
She says he cannot carry the real body. The real body is somewhere.
But the body he is carrying is just an ordinary body.
But it is somebody's body.
She knows what she is saying. She is not a kid.
Say, ''In the name of Jesus'' and put her on the floor.
In the name of Jesus!
The job is done. She is running from her father now.
If you go near to her, she will run. Go near her.
Because you have done something now. Run after her!
Call her now!
Come here!
Because she cannot go near him.
Before now, she tossed you like bread. You used to see her in your dreams.
Yes, Man of God.
Now, she cannot go near you.
She will not be able to go home with you unless she is delivered.
What she is seeing now is light. She is afraid.
You can't carry her again because she will not even follow you unless she is delivered.
Because you are not for her again.
Go and wait there.
This is what everybody needs.
Go this way!
Go and meet your dad!
Meet your dad!
Move close.
In the name of Jesus!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Vivian Prince Wilson.
I'm from Nigeria but residing in South Africa.
The man standing beside me is my dad.
The problem that brought us to The SCOAN was that
I was possessed with the spirit of witchcraft.
It all started when we visited a woman in 2009.
She offered us a drink and since then, I'd been seeing a demon following me.
There was a time we were watching the news and a man had a plane crash
and survived by drinking his own urine.
After that, I went to the toilet but my dad never knew what I had in mind to do.
When I got there, that demon told me that I should urinate in a bowl and drink.
I did so and flushed an empty toilet.
Since that time, I had been drinking my own urine.
The demon also pushed me to eat my hair, pick my nose
and eat the wax from my ears.
That made me to also start biting my finger nails.
By that time, I was very big and fat.
As you can see now, I have lost so much weight.
The demon pushed me into doing so many things that affected my dad's career.
By now, he was supposed to be in England but because I was possessed
with the spirit of witchcraft, I made it not to happen.
Anytime he picked me from school, I would always look dirty.
I was also addicted to eating sand.
That demon liked everywhere to be dirty.
It went to the extent that I could stay two months without taking my shower.
My mum would force me to take a shower before I would agree.
Even when I would be taking a shower, I would be very angry with her.
Glory be to God, I have been delivered!
Since my deliverance, I've been relating with my parents and younger ones.
That spirit gave me the spirit of anger.
Anytime my mother or father would talk to me, I would get angry at them and abuse them.
Now, I am relating with them and I am very light.
And I have lost so much weight.
I thank God for delivering me.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Prince Wilson Olomu.
I'm a Nigerian based in South Africa.
As you have seen in the clip, that day was a wonderful day in my life.
It started in South Africa when we were watching Emmanuel TV
when the man of God was praying during the mass prayer.
My daughter started manifesting; she started vomiting and coughing.
I confronted her and asked, ''Who are you? What is wrong with you?''
Then the evil spirit in her started speaking and said a lot of things.
I decided to bring her to The SCOAN for proper deliverance.
The day we came, what happened is what you saw in the clip.
There were a lot of things happening to her before her deliverance.
She was eating a lot of things which human beings don't eat.
She ate the hair of every part of her body, sniffed petrol and ate dirt -
she ate a lot of things human beings don't eat.
That caused her to be fat as you saw in the clip.
A lot of problems happened in my marriage and career.
She was very aggressive to her younger ones
and would always see her mother as her rival and not as her mother.
She hated her mum; she hated me as well.
She would always appear to me in my dreams, attacking me in various ways.
She would attack my career as well.
You brought her here after the spirit within her manifested when watching Emmanuel TV.
Now we've seen what happened in the clip.
Tell us, ever since this deliverance, what are the changes?
Since her deliverance, there have been a lot of changes in the entire family
and in her life as well.
Any day I am not at home, she is like the father in the house.
She takes care of her mum and younger ones.
She does things that you will know truly, deliverance has taken place in her life
and God has imparted to her divine wisdom
that she behaves like a normal child ought to behave.
Wow! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
So you mean ever since then your daughter has been behaving completely nornally,
she's very intelligent in school, she's now loving the family
and behaving completely like a normal child?
Yes, sir. And I have a clip of how she looks now.
This is the very person you saw in the clip.
Wow! Thank You, Jesus Christ. Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
You said before, she used to eat many strange things,
she used to attack you in the dream. Tell us, have all of those things stopped?
Yes, all those things have stopped.
Presently, she is the neatest in the family.
Anything dirty seriously irritates her as a result of her deliverance.
As a result of this deliverance, there is a lot of peace in my marriage now and in my career.
As a result of that deliverance, I was able to have my own house
in South Africa which I bought without owing anything.
My family and I are able to have a permanent residence in South Africa.
I can show you the picture of my family.
This is the certificate of the proof of our permanent residence in South Africa.
The whole family.
This is my ID from South Africa.
My career has been great after the deliverance.
Before the deliverance, my legs were swollen
and I could not even use them as a soccer player.
But after the deliverance, when I went back home,
without using any medication, everything went back to normal
and I was restored to the one God had created me.
Thank You, Jesus Christ! We can just hear the blessings that God has brought into this family.
Sir, you even said that as we saw in the clip, your daughter was very fat
because of the things she was eating and how this evil spirit was occupying her body.
But right now, how is her health and her body?
She is perfectly well in terms of her health now.
Regarding her body, you have seen the picture of her -
how she looks slim and tall.
Ok, we can see again here the picture of that little girl we saw manifesting earlier
and indeed, this is the evidence that Jesus Christ has completely delivered her.
Some years after the deliverance, you can see that she is completely back to nornal.
We give all the glory to God Almighty.
My advice to viewers around the world and the people present here
is that as a parent, when the man of God is praying,
don't concentrate only on yourself or your wife.
The children are very important. Bring them around you
because the devil is a very trickish spirit; he will take them away.
You will think that they are playing
but satan doesn't want them to receive their deliverance.
Make sure that they are around you;
pray with them and you will see the hand of God in their lives.
My second advice is: viewers all over the world
and the people present here, let our prayers always be,
'If God sends the man of God to deliver you,
may you receive your deliverance anywhere you are
because distance is not a barrier'.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ.
Indeed, distance is not a barrier.
We believe our brother's advice is a great encouragement to viewers around the world.
During the course of today's service, Prophet TB Joshua will begin to pray for the viewers.
Wherever you are, join by faith, connect with our prayer,
bring your family together and allow the anointing of God to touch you
wherever you are in the world and you too will share your own testimony.
Brother, we encourage you to continue to bring up this beautiful girl and your family
in the ways of the Lord, and definitely the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.